// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Has Mrs. Smith arrived ..... ?",
    answer: "A) yet",
    options: [
      "A) yet",
      "B) still",
      "C) now",
      "D) already",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Wendy is ..... Paul to get up now.",
    answer: "A) telling",
    options: [
      "A) telling",
      "B) saying",
      "C) saying to",
      "D) telling to",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Have you sent that letter to Mr. Taylor? Yes, I've ..... done that.",
    answer: "C) already",
    options: [
      "A) still",
      "B) yet",
      "C) already",
      "D) now",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "It's no use ..... to him. He doesn't listen.",
    answer: "A) speaking",
    options: [
      "A) speaking",
      "B) to speak",
      "C) spoke",
      "D) have spoken",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "This is the girl ..... I met on Thursday.",
    answer: "D)  -----",
    options: [
      "A) whom",
      "B)  which",
      "C)  what",
      "D)  -----",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " ..... is your house from here?",
    answer: "C) How far",
    options: [
      "A) How much",
      "B) How long",
      "C) How far",
      "D) How many",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "You can watch TV ..... you like.",
    answer: "A) whenever",
    options: [
      "A) whenever",
      "B) soon",
      "C) always",
      "D) whatever",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "This house is quite old. It ..... in 1910.",
    answer: "B)  was built",
    options: [
      "A) built",
      "B)  was built",
      "C)  build",
      "D)  has built",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "She ..... go to school yesterday.",
    answer: "B) had to",
    options: [
      "A) must",
      "B) had to",
      "C) ought to",
      "D) should have",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "That's the ..... of my worries, it'll never happen.",
    answer: "D)  least",
    options: [
      "A) fewer",
      "B)  less",
      "C)  last",
      "D)  least",
    ]
  },

];